Hello Hello Friends Namaskar Body Solution
Welcome Friends in today's video
we are going to know how retention from alien swelling
happens and
what documents and how much thing has to be
used for it,
you will get complete information in this video,
friends first of all let me tell you that the
documents required for this are
your passport size photo and
your PAN card Aadhar card and
qualification proof, you will have to scan it and
keep it on your system and its size
friends minimum 20k and maximum
is fine for labor department and before that
friends and once you have to keep in mind
that the special session which is free friends
is 1200 and in this offer the government and State
together have given this, friends it is of egg
because this is a frill service offer,
after this friends it reduces or there is
interest, hence it depends on Sita, so
friends if you are new to our
channel then subscribe to our channel
because whenever
we will bring more information videos for you, then
You will get a notification and you
can take advantage of it by watching that video
and after that friends I
would like to tell you one more thing if you like this video then
like it, comment
and set it so that your friends can
know about it and they can
take advantage of this video. Okay so without delay
friends we will start the video.
Now
friends what you have to do is
take your CSC photo, you have to login first
but after doing this friends
this is the search bar, you have to see insurance,
I am safe, thank you friends you have to press in it,
okay press enter and search and
show me,
hello friends right now
we have gone through this page for a full week, so what to do first
friends you have to follow back and come down completely,
after going down friends
you can see here there is also an alien
station, you have to click on
Ajay,
but friends this color gets opened here, in this
friends what you have to do is it is
written now balance balance
registration, in this you have to click on clear,
after clicking friends see our
retention introduction has opened, in this
friends already our CID  That club has been done,
now we have to enter all our personal
information in it, so first of all
you have to enter your first
name, after entering your Midland, later
National club, after that friends, in this
father's name you have to enter your Aadhar number, in this
mother's name and you
also have to enter your email ID and after that mobile
number details outside, your gender is Dual,
so you have to
choose your religion, after that it is cut, okay
and you can see that friends,
you have to upload your passport size photo in the
browser and
as I told you, its
size should
also be a mixture of 80, okay and
after that, you have to bring your qualification,
friends, see, you are from class 10 to
PG, after that friends, you have to enter your
address completely,
okay friends, at the bottom,
I will give you your ID proof,
Aadhar card or pain killer, all Aadhar card,
DL, passport, ration card, photo, Reddy, anything,
You have to use it and
enter two numbers in it,
after that friends, you have to upload the document through browser, if you
see then
open it and enter the number in it,
after that you have to upload it on your pande, after that
friends see, the
education proof is that much you have to
upload your certificate qualification certificate in it, after that
friends see, whenever our 15 is completed,
after completion friends see,
you have to do it on possible, okay,
when friends after our submission,
friends, it will take you to your payment site, in that
you have to enter your password,
after entering the password,
enter your paypal, the payment is completed,
after that friends, you have to
call messenger Smt Ashraf first, in that friends,
your station ID, your CCR is
Station RD and the password will be
your mobile number, please friends,
send a message for us, madam, we have to
complete it, it is present and
for us, every human being has to
study for one hour after lunch, if you
people do not study  If you want to do it, then
you have to keep it open for one hour
because it has a time limit. What happened? Okay,
now
and after that, friends, after our entire Malik is
completed,
after completing the test, friends,
our receipt gets excited.
After the certificate is completed, friends, whatever
decisions we have made regarding our insurance,
they are automatically tested, whatever is left
out of digital, it gets done automatically at that time
and we
can access all the insurance options. So
friends, I have told you the entire topic of your video
in the video. So
friends, if you liked this video, then
you can like it once or comment. Keep it,
friends, let people visit. Once again
I repeat one more thing, friends, if
you have not subscribed to our channel
yet, then subscribe because whenever
we bring this video for you, you will get
information for the whole week. See you again
friends with a new video. Jai Hind,
Jai Bharat.